Guide to the Department of Military Science and Tactics, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Military Science and Tactics, Yale University, student records
1949-1963
RU 814
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
13.75
(11 boxes)
The records consist of student records, examinations, and miscellaneous materials documenting the Military Science and Tactics Department at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Military Science and Tactics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 42-A (YRG 42-A), Records of military training programs at Yale.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records, examinations, and miscellaneous materials documenting the Military Science and Tactics Department at Yale.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by class year.
College students; Military education; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Dept. of Military Science and Tactics
- Student records, circa 1949-1963; Accession 19ND-A-168
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039.
  - Miscellaneous, 1949-1952 (Box 1)
  - 1953-1954 Mui (Box 2)
  - 1954 Mui - 1955 Fi (Box 3)
  - 1955 Po - 1955 Ni (Box 4)
  - 1955 No - 1956 Ca (Box 5)
  - 1956 eh - 1956 Sf (Box 6)
  - 1956 Sm - 1957 McG (Box 7)
  - 1957 McK - 1958 Du (Box 8)
  - 1958 Fa - 1958 Zu (Box 9)
  - 1959 An - 1959 Va (Box 10)
  - 1959 Vo - 1963 Y (Box 11)